storynory.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy | Free Audio Stories For Kids @ Storynory

We try to make our site as safe and enjoyable for you and your children as possible. To give you the best possible service, it is necessary for us to collect certain information about you. This policy tells you how we collect information about you and how we protect it.

We are particularly keen not to obtain the personal addresses of children under the age of 13. We ask that in all email communications with us, you use the address of somebody who is at least 13 years old. This policy is to reassure parents and guardians that Storynory is a safe site for their children to use.

**Control of Information** Storynory is owned by Blog Relations Limited, 26 Star St, London W2 1QB, . Any information collected by Storynory is controlled by Blog Relations Limited (”we/us/our”). Your point of contact for privacy issues is Hugh Fraser: hugh@blog-relations.com. Telephone +44 (0)20 7706 7974.

Many of our Web pages contain links to external Web sites outside the control of Blog Relations Limited. Please be aware that when you follow a link to another site, you are then subject to the privacy policies of the new site.

**Feedback and Forum** Many sites request users to fill in an email address in order to take part in feedback forums. Storynory does NOT request an email address from those leaving comments and we ask that users fill in a first name only. This policy is to reassure visitors that Storynory is a safe environment for children to explore and use.

**Automatic Collection for information** : When you visit our site, we automatically collect and store the following information:

* the date and time  
* the originating IP address (a number assigned to your computer when you access the Web).  
* the type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser)  
* the URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser)  
* the object requested  
* completion status of the request  
* pages visited

In many cases and a particular IP address will indicate a geographic region in which the computer is located.

**How the Information is Used** : We use the information that we collect automatically to measure the number of visitors to the different areas of our sites, and to help us make our sites more useful to visitors. This includes analyzing these logs periodically to determine the traffic through our servers, the number of pages served, and the level of demand for pages and topics of interest. For example, Awstats is one of the statistical programs we use to analyze the data that we collect automatically.

**How Long is the Information Retained** : The logs may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way necessary to prevent security breaches and to insure the integrity of the data on our servers.

**Safeguarding your personal information** If you enter into a financial transaction with us, a record of the transaction will be maintained by [Paypal ](https://www.paypal.com/)in a secure area which we can access. Bertie’s Birthday Stories have are subject to their own [terms and conditions](http://storynory.com/terms-and-conditions/) to take account of information you may send us to complete the transaction.

**Email** By sending us an electronic mail message you may be sending us personally-identifying information. In these cases, we may retain the information as long as necessary to respond to your request or otherwise resolve the subject matter of your e-mail.

In particular you may be sending us pictures or other user generated content. We will delete your email after the content has been posted to the site.

Please be aware that email is not necessarily secure from interception or misdirection.

If you enter an email address into any of our forms (such as email subscription or e-cards), or send us an email, we ask that you use the address of somebody who is at least 13 years or older. Typically this would the address of a parent or guardian.

**Children Under the age of 13** Children may view our site and download our stories freely. NON Personally Identifiable Information will be collected from them automatically and included in the general statistics about visitors to our site. There is no way for us to determine the age of a visitor.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 directly from the site.

**User Generated Content** We encourage users to send us children’s content including pictures, jokes and stories.

If you send us a child’s picture or story or other content, all we need to know is the following: child’s first name, age, M or F, country. This is the information that we will publish along side the content. Please send the content to us from an adult’s email address - and NOT from an email address belonging to a child under 13 years of age.

Your email will be retained ONLY as long as it is needed to post the content to the site (see above notice concerning email). We will NOT collect and store any information from your email (such as your email address and your family name) which might be used to personally identify the child. This information will be deleted.

**Future use of user generated content** As we are unable to retain personal data about users, you must note that we won’t be able to inform you personally if we re-publish any content you send us in a new format. For that reason, it is important that you familiarise yourself with the copyright page before sending us any content so that you are aware how we may use it in future.

**Cookies** This site uses cookies. Cookies are small files that Web servers place on a user’s hard drive. Cookies have several functions:

* they allow the Web site to identify you as a previous visitor each time you access a site;  
* they track what information you view at a site (important to commercial sites trying to determine your buying preferences);  
* in the more advanced cases they track your movements through many Web sites but not the whole Web;  
* businesses use them for customer convenience to allow them to produce a list of items to buy and pay for them all at one time and to garner information about what individuals are buying at their sites;  
* advertisers use them to determine the effectiveness of their marketing and offer insights into consumer preferences and tastes by collecting data from many Web sites; and  
* they can be used to help a Web site tailor screens for each customer’s preference.

If you are concerned about the potential use of the information gathered from your computer by cookies, you can set your browser to prompt you before it accepts a cookie. Most Internet browsers have settings that let you identify and/or reject cookies.

**Information Protection**  
We will take reasonable precaution to protect any information we receive such that contained in emails until such time as it is deleted.

**Jurisdiction** This agreement is governed by the laws of the United Kingdom and any litigation or dispute arising from it will be settled in a UK Court of law.

**Future change of Privacy Policy** This Policy was last updated on 19th August 2007. If we need to change this policy in future, we will draw attention to the change on our site in a way that is clearly noticeable.

This policy was last updated to take account of financial transactions with us.
